<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Topic Film Lists</title>
        <link>https://pixly.app/topics</link>
        <description>Updates on changes and additions to police beat central.</description>
        <atom:link href="https://pixly.app/feed/" rel="self"></atom:link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 16:04:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title>The Most Controversial Movies of All Times</title>
            <link>https://pixly.app/topic/controversial-films</link>
            <description>The movies that shock,thrill, and  provoke the audiences and cause public disagreements on specific issue.</description>
            <guid>https://pixly.app/topic/controversial-films</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Best LGBTQ+ Movies of All Times</title>
            <link>https://pixly.app/topic/lgbtq-plus-films</link>
            <description>LGBT movement has gained their civil right in many countries, after many centuries of persecution, shame, suppression, and secrecy. We have entered a time which there is plenty of LGBT movies are releasing in mainstream. Starting from the 2010's, queer cinema's influence evolved towards a more unive</description>
            <guid>https://pixly.app/topic/lgbtq-plus-films</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Great Feeling Good Movies That Leaves Warm Feeling On You</title>
            <link>https://pixly.app/topic/feel-good-movies</link>
            <description>Some films remind us what is valuable, what we have is more valuable than what we don't have. Here, the movies leaves warm feelings and good vibes on you.</description>
            <guid>https://pixly.app/topic/feel-good-movies</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pixly- The Great Movies That Passed The Bechdel Test</title>
            <link>https://pixly.app/topic/bechdel-test</link>
            <description>Although it is not a perfect test or perfect indicator, it is a test that used as an indicator for the active presence of women in the fiction and to call attention to gender inequality.</description>
            <guid>https://pixly.app/topic/bechdel-test</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Great Mind Blowing / Thought Provoking Movies</title>
            <link>https://pixly.app/topic/thought-provoking</link>
            <description>As the world's most complex art form, cinema offers us new ideas, new ways of thinking about something. Although it is very important to gaining a new ideas, the more important thing is to rethink what we assume is we already know.</description>
            <guid>https://pixly.app/topic/thought-provoking</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>